I was put in prison because I'm a transgender woman, but now I'm free.
I went with another trans woman, we're having dinner, and then police cops, they came down,
they stood in front of us and asked us our national identity card.
As a transgender woman, I don't usually work my ID because what I portray is not what you're going to say on my ID.
Today, after then, they asked us to follow them. We got into the car, and the commissioner asked me,
are you Shakiro? I said, yes, I'm Shakiro. He said he's going to send me to jail.
I immediately asked him, why? Why are you going to send me to jail?
He said, don't you know what you're doing? You are an abomination.
You are spoiling the youth, you are spoiling children, all of the stuff you publish on your social media platforms.
I remember the day I was sentenced to five years in prison, and I almost collapsed.
I was sentenced because of attempted homosexuality and public indecency.
That was, that was the charges against me.
You are like surrounded. I was traumatized. I can't count the number of...